STUDENT AT FIB - UPC OF BACHELOR DEGREE IN INFORMATICS ENGINEERING MAJOR IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Barcelona - Spain

🛮 🖰 (+34) 638 25 59 90 | 💌 andreugallofre@gmail.com | 🖸 atsuky | 🛅 andreugallofre | 💆 @andreugallofre | 🦠

About Me

I was born on Dec 23rd, 1994 in Barcelona. I am a 24 year old student, currently in my last year of a Bachelor Degree in Computer Engineering, with major in Software Engineering at FIB - UPC. I worked for almost 3 years in Nexica as Support and Java developer and currently I am working in Capside as Sysops Engineer.

I like learning new thinks and taking new challenges. Also, I am organizer of HackUPC, the biggest student hackathon in Europe, leading the HackerXperience team.

Education

UPC (Universitat Politécnica de Catalunya) - FIB

Barcelona

BACHELOR DEGREE IN INFORMATICS ENGINEERING

Sept. 2015 - Present

- · Specialized in Software Engineering.
- · Bases on project management, Multitier architecture, Design Patterns, Object Oriented Programming, Software Arquitecture.
- Prepared for beeing a Full-Stack developer and work with agile methodologies.

Escola professional Salesians de Sarrià

Barcelona

GRAU SUPERIOR - SYSTEM ADMINISTRATION AND NETWORKING

Sept. 2013 - Present

Work Experience_

CAPSIDE Barcelona

SYSOPS ENGINEER Feb. 2018 - Present

· Working on the internal projects team, developing tools to improve the eficiency of the engineers of the others teams.

Nexica Barcelona

JAVA DEVELOPER March 2017 - Feb. 2018

- Developer of the corporative application:
- Technologies used:
 - Java EE, CDI, JPA, JSF/Primefaces, Spring, Hibernate, JMS
 - Eclipse, Maven, Subversion, Sonar

NexicaBarcelona

IT SUPPORT ENGINEER Oct. 2014 - March 2017

- Direct contact with the final costumer (Danone, Vueling, Generalitat de Catalunya, Iberostar etc) based on comunicative skills, spoken and written, that supports a philosphy based on the Customer Intimacy.
- Tech and solutions used:
- Brocade Load Balancer, VisionApp, VMware solutions (vCloud Director and vSphere), MySQL, SQL, Exchange, Certificates, Linux (Apache and Tomcat), Postfix y Cisco ASA

Extracurricular Activity_

HackUPC Barcelona

HACKERXPERIENCE DIRECTOR 2017 - Present

organizer of HackUPC, the biggest student hackathon in Europe, currently leading the HackerXperience team trying to make the experience of all participants in the event the best as possible, but participated in other roles, like Sponsorship, where the main task were look for companies that wants to sponsor the event

Tecnologia per Tothom Barcelona

VOLUNTEER 2018 - Present

Volunteer in the club TxT, where we try to bring the new technologies to people that do not have access to it. We recover computers and other devices that the companies don't need anymore and we repair them and send to ONG's

October 2019 Andreu Gallofré i Bahon



PROGRAMING LANGUAGES

Advanced Skills: Java, C++, C, SQL, JavaScript, PowerShell

Familiar: Ruby, Phython, C#, Assambler x86, MIPS, R, PL/PgSQL, Bash.

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATION

Proficient: Windows, Linux, AWS, DNS, Mail, VMware **Advanced Skills:** Azure, GCP, DHCP, Cisco, Routing

Familiar: Kubernetes

MISCELLANEOUS

Advanced Skills: HTML, CSS, XML, Markdown, LaTex.

Intermidiate: OpenGL.

Languages _____

Catalan: Native/BilingualLevel CSpanish: Native/BilingualLevel CEnglish: Upper-IntermediateLevel B2

Others____

LICENCES

Driving lisence: B since July 2013

PRIZES AND AWARDS

Nov. 2018	Best hack hosted on domain.com and Category winner: https://linkd.in/d-2suv3	JacobsHack
Nov. 2018	Semic Prize - HackEPS 2018: First team to solve the algorithmic challenge proposed by Semic	HackEPS 2018
March 2018	Winner of ThinkBig by Telefonica: https://github.com/atsuky/EasyBicing	HackMobility
March 2017	Barclays challenge winner: https://dvp.st/2mivxbP	StudentHack V

CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Cloud Practicioner: https://bit.ly/35QJKrw